Guide to the James Lees-Milne Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1923-97; Series I; 7.35; (18 boxes)
  - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE
    - Bryant, Arthur, Sir, 1964, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Bryant, Julius, 1986 May 22 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Buccleuch, Mary, Duchess of; Buccleuch, Walter, Duke of, 1956-85, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Buckle, Richard, 1993-95 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Bulmer-Thomas, Ivor, 1988 Jul 24 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Burden-Muller, Rowland, 1975 May 15 (Box 2, Folder 104)
      Letter is to mutual friend
      Sonia, with cover letter
      from her to JL-M
    - Burkett, M. E., 1980 Nov 19 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Bury, Mairi, Lady, 1992 Nov 17 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Butler of Saffron Walden, Richard Austen Butler, Baron, 1971 Sep 6 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Byrne, John, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Byron, Robert, 1933-40 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - "C" general, 1934-95 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Calloway, Stephen, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Card, Tim, 1991-95 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Carew, Denis, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Casey, T. A., 1987-88 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Cattaui, Georges, 1933-39 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Cave, Graham, 1986-87 (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - Cavendish, Elizabeth, Lady ("Feeble") (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - Champneys, Basil, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - Chancellor, Edward, 1989 Mar 12 (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - Chancellor, Silvia, 1989-91 (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - Chaney, Edward, 1987-94 (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - Chaplin, Rosemary, 1988, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Charles, Prince of Wales, 1987 Dec 21 (Box 2, Folder 123)
      Written by a secretary
    - Charles Scribner's Sons, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Charleston Trust, 1988-97 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Charmley, John, 1983-87 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Chatel, Lawrence, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Chatsworth House Trust (Devonshire Collections), 1959-94 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Chatto and Windus, 1971-90 (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Chatwin, Bruce; Chatwin, Elizabeth, 1983-96 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Chatwynd, John, 1992-93 (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - Cheetham, John, 1985-96, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - Chetwode, Penelope, 1933, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Cheyne, Joseph, Sir, 1981-85 (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - Chipcase, Paul, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Cholmondeley, Sybil; Cholmondeley, George Horatio Charles Cholmondeley, 5th Marquess of, 1960-86 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Christie's, 1989-97 (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - Churchill, Diana Spencer, 1928, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - Churchill, John Spencer, 1928-91, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - Churchill, Randolph Spencer, 1923-28, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - Cigogna, Anna-Maria, 1987-94, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Clark, Alan, 1983-96 (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - Clark, Ethne, 1988 Nov 3 (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - Clark, Kenneth, 1939-78 (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - Clary-Aldringen, Alfons (Prince Clary); Clary-Aldringen, Lidi, 1967-78 (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - Clemens, Cyril, 1977-78 (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - Clifton-Taylor, Alec, 1948-84 (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - Clonmore, William, Lord, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - Coats, Peter, 1984-88 (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - Cockerell, Sydney Carlyle, Sir, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - Colefax, Sibyl, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - Colegate, Isabel, 1980-97 (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - Colette, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 153)
      Copy of letter to Violet Trefusis
    - Collins Publishers (Harper Collins), 1982-95 (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - Colwin, Howard, 1951-67 (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - Combe, Silvia, 1994, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 156)
    - Compton-Burnett, Ivy, 1945-68 (Box 3, Folder 157)
    - Compton Russell, Ltd., 1975 Jan 25 (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - Conant, Kenneth John, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - Congreve, Ambrose; Congreve, [Marjorie?], 1997 Jun 22, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - Conklin, Gary, 1987-94 (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - Cooke, Ashley; Cooke, Frances, 1975-95 (Box 3, Folder 162)
    - Coombs, Barbara, 1992-93 (Box 3, Folder 163)
    - Cooper, Artemis, 1984-95 (Box 3, Folder 164)
    - Cooper, Diana, Lady, [1945?], 1981 (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - Corbett, Elizabeth, 1957-93 (Box 3, Folder 166)
    - Cornforth, John, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 167)
    - Council for the Protection of Rural England, 1968-93 (Box 3, Folder 168)
    - Country Life, 1991-94 (Box 3, Folder 169)
    - Country Living, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 170)
    - Coveney, James, 1988-89 (Box 3, Folder 171)
    - Coward-McCann, Inc., 1970-71 (Box 3, Folder 172)
    - Cox, Trenchard, 1973, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 173)
    - Cozzi, Gaetano
      See: Series II, Writings, The Age of Inigo Jones, Box 19, folder 888
    - Crawford and Balcarres, Robert Alexander Lindsay, Earl of, 1950-71 (Box 3, Folder 174)
    - Creston, Dormer (Doreen Colston- Baynes), 1939-62, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 175)
      Some are copies of letters
      given to Simon Baynes by
      JL-M in 1980
    - Crichton, J. D., 1951 Jul 30 (Box 3, Folder 176)
    - Crocker, Walter R., 1981 Dec 14 (Box 3, Folder 177)
    - Croft, Henry Page, 1940 May 23 (Box 3, Folder 178)
    - Croft-Murray, Edward, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 179)
    - Croome, W. I., 1963-67 (Box 3, Folder 180)
    - Cross, Robert S., 1996 Feb 23 (Box 3, Folder 181)
    - Crowdy, M. C., 1992, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 182)
    - Crum, J. M. C., 1951 (Box 3, Folder 183)
    - Curteis, Ian, 1990-95 (Box 3, Folder 184)
    - Curtis Brown Group Ltd., 1983-87 (Box 3, Folder 185)
    - Curtis, Anthony, 1997 Nov 11 (Box 3, Folder 186)
    - "D" general, 1931-96 (Box 4, Folder 187)
    - Daily Mail, 1997, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 188)
    - Daily Telegraph, 1984-88, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 189)
    - Dale, Antony, 1948 Aug 15 (Box 4, Folder 190)
    - Dalley, Jan, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 190a)
    - Dalmeyer, Ursula Balfour, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 191)
    - Dance, Monica, 1951-96 (Box 4, Folder 192)
    - D'Arcy, Martin Cyril, 1933-75 (Box 4, Folder 193)
    - David Hingham Associates Ltd., 1965-97 (Box 4, Folder 194-195)
    - Davidson, Mary, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 196)
    - Davies, Randall, 1940 Apr 7 (Box 4, Folder 197)
    - Davis, Terence, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 198)
    - Day Lewis, Cecil, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 199)
      Addressed "Dear Keith"
    - Debrett's Distinguished People of Today, 1987-91 (Box 4, Folder 200)
    - De-la-Noy, Michael, 1984-97 (Box 4, Folder 201)
    - Dentler, Clara Louise, 1971 Nov 27 (Box 4, Folder 202)
    - Derwent, George Harcourt Johnstone, Lord, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 203)
    - Devonshire, Deborah Vivien Freeman- Mitford Cavendish, Duchess of, 1968-87 (Box 4, Folder 204)
    - Devonshire, Andrew Robert Buxton Cavendish, Duke of, 1985-86 (Box 4, Folder 205)
    - Di Carcaci, Diana, 1996 May 19 (Box 4, Folder 206)
    - Dickinson, Patric, 1988-97 (Box 4, Folder 207)
    - Dickinson, Richard, 1996-97 (Box 4, Folder 208)
    - Dickson, Elizabeth, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 209)
    - Dinshaw, Candia, 199[0?], 1994 (Box 4, Folder 210)
    - Dix, George, 1981-92 (Box 4, Folder 211)
    - Dixon, Allan St. John, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 212)
    - Dods, Espie, 1983 May 28 (Box 4, Folder 213)
    - Donaldson, Frances Lonsdale, Lady; Donaldson, Jack, 1970-94 (Box 4, Folder 214)
    - Douglas-Home, Jessica, 1990-96 (Box 4, Folder 215)
    - Dovecote Press, 1988-94 (Box 4, Folder 216)
    - Downside Abbey, 1986-94 (Box 4, Folder 217)
    - Drinkwater, Derek, 1977-94 (Box 4, Folder 218)
    - Drogheda, Garrett Moore, Earl of; Drogheda, Joan Moore, 1968-75, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 219)
    - Drury, Martin; Drury, Liz, 1991-97 (Box 4, Folder 220)
      See also: National Trust, Box 12, folder 566
    - Dufferin and Ava, Basil Sheridan Hamilton-Temple-Blackwood, 4th Marquess of, 1927-29 (Box 4, Folder 221)
    - Dufferin and Ava, Sheridan Frederick Terence Hamilton-Temple-Blackwood, 5th Marquess of (Box 4, Folder 222)
    - Dunning, Robert W., 1990 May 24 (Box 4, Folder 223)
    - Dutton, Ralph, 1951-72 (Box 4, Folder 224)
    - "E" general, 1969-96 (Box 4, Folder 225)
    - Edwards, Ralph, 1957-70 (Box 4, Folder 226)
    - Eeles, Adrian; Eeles, Lucretia, 1990-95, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 227)
    - Eisdale, Edmund, 1948-93 (Box 4, Folder 228)
    - Egremont, Max, 1982-93 (Box 4, Folder 229)
    - Elizabeth II, Queen of Great Britain, 1983, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 230)
      Letters written by secretaries
    - Emerson, John, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 231)
    - Esher, Lionel (4th Viscount), 1965-93 (Box 5, Folder 232)
    - Esher, Oliver Sylvain Baliol Brett, 3rd Viscount, 1942-62 (Box 5, Folder 233)
    - Esher, Reginald Baliol Brett, 2nd Viscount
      See: Series II, Writings, The Enigmatic Edwardian, Box 21, folder 909
    - Etchells, Frederick, 1967 Dec 31 (Box 5, Folder 234)
    - Eton College Library, 1992 Jun 4 (Box 5, Folder 235)
      Outgoing letter from JL-M
      to Mr. Meredith
    - Evans, David Morgan, 1995 Apr 18 (Box 5, Folder 236)
    - Evans, Illtud, 1966-70 (Box 5, Folder 237)
    - Evans, Joan, 1961-76 (Box 5, Folder 238)
    - Eyles, John, n.y., Feb 4 (Box 5, Folder 239)
    - "F" general, 1933-97 (Box 5, Folder 240)
    - Faber and Faber, 1936-88 (Box 5, Folder 241)
    - Fairfax-Lucy, Alice, 1980-93, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 242)
    - Fairfax-Lucy, Edmund, Sir, [1994], n.d. (Box 5, Folder 243)
    - Fallowell, Duncan, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 244)
    - Fane, Julian, 1978-97 (Box 5, Folder 245)
    - Farrer, Peter, 1991 May 5 (Box 5, Folder 246)
    - Fawcett, E. C. R., n.d. (Box 5, Folder 247)
    - Fedden, Robin, 1979, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 248)
    - Feray, Jean, 1989 Nov 26 (Box 5, Folder 249)
    - Fergusson, Jamie, 1985-97, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 250)
      See also: Series II, Writings, Correspondence of Harold Nicolson, Enid Bagnold, Box 23, folder 942
    - Fermor, Patrick Leigh, 1981-91 (Box 5, Folder 251)
    - Festing, Sally, 1983 Apr 20 (Box 5, Folder 252)
    - The Field, 1985-94 (Box 5, Folder 253)
    - Fisher, Clive, 1992 Mar 7 (Box 5, Folder 254)
    - Fitzalan, Lord, 1934-41 (Box 5, Folder 255)
    - Fitzgerald, Desmond, 1977 Apr 16 (Box 5, Folder 256)
    - Fleetwood-Hesketh, Peter, 1963-84 (Box 5, Folder 257)
    - Fleming, John, 1986, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 258)
    - Fletcher, Hanslip, 1940 Mar 26 (Box 5, Folder 259)
    - Forbes, Alastair, 1976-85 (Box 5, Folder 260)
    - Forbes-Adam, Colin, 1937-50, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 261)
    - Ford, Brinsley, 1981-95 (Box 5, Folder 262)
      See also: Series II, Writings, The Last Stuarts, Box 24, folder 966
    - Ford, David, 1982 Mar 11 (Box 5, Folder 263)
    - Foster, John, 1994-96 (Box 5, Folder 264)
    - Fothergill, Brian; Fothergill, Miles, 1971-90 (Box 5, Folder 265)
    - Foyle, Christina (W. & G. Foyle Ltd.), 1977-97 (Box 5, Folder 266)
    - Franklin, Colin, 1985 Jul 19 (Box 5, Folder 267)
    - Freeman, David, 1986-97 (Box 5, Folder 268)
    - Freer, Stephen, 1995 Mar 18 (Box 5, Folder 269)
    - Friends of Mt. Athos, 1992-96 (Box 5, Folder 270)
    - Fryer, Jonathan, 1980 Nov 8 (Box 5, Folder 271)
    - Fulford, Roger, 1947-80, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 272)
    - Fuller, Peter, 1989 Mar 28 (Box 5, Folder 273)
    - "G" general, 1933-97 (Box 5, Folder 274)
    - G. Heywood Hill Ltd., 1958-97 (Box 5, Folder 275)
    - Gallagher, Tom, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 276)
    - Garnett, Oliver
      See: National Trust, Box 12, folder 566
    - Gascoigne, Bamber; Gascoigne, Christina, 1979-95 (Box 5, Folder 277)
    - Gascoigne, Midi, 1933-90, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 278)
    - Gascoigne, Veronica, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 279)
    - Gatty, Charles Neilson, 1992 Jan 30 (Box 5, Folder 280)
    - Gaynor, Cathy, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 281)
    - Gaze, John, 1983-86 (Box 5, Folder 282)
    - George Rainbird Ltd., 1965-82 (Box 6, Folder 283)
    - The Georgian Group, 1976-97 (Box 6, Folder 284)
    - Gibbs, Elise, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 285)
    - Gibson, Pat, Lord, 1983-84 (Box 6, Folder 286)
      See also: Magdalen College, Box 11, folder 506
    - Gibson, Thomas, 1994-[97] (Box 6, Folder 287)
    - Gielgud, John, Sir, 1933, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 288)
    - Gilbert, Christopher, 1987 Jan 15 (Box 6, Folder 289)
    - Gilbert, Martin, 1974-87 (Box 6, Folder 290)
    - Gill, Brendan, 1973 May 3 (Box 6, Folder 291)
    - Gillman, Daniel H. (Box 6, Folder 292)
    - [Gioeninx?], Pico van Zoelen, Baron, 1993, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 293)
    - Girard, Didier, 1989-97 (Box 6, Folder 294)
    - Girouard, Mark, 1986-87 (Box 6, Folder 295)
    - Gladwyn, Lord, 1978, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 296)
    - Glasgow Museums and Art Galleries, 1985-96 (Box 6, Folder 297)
    - Glendinning, Victoria, 1981-83 (Box 6, Folder 298)
    - Gloag, John, 1974, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 299)
    - Gloucestershire Gardens and Landscape Trust, 1994-96 (Box 6, Folder 300)
    - Goodman, Ariane (Ariane Bankes), 1991-96, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 301)
      See also: Collins Publishers, Box 3, folder 154
      See also: John Murray, Ltd., Box 8, folder 409
    - Goodman, Celia, 1996 Nov 11 (Box 6, Folder 302)
    - Gordon, Archie (Marquess of Aberdeen), 1974-84 (Box 6, Folder 303)
    - Gore, Bobby, 1990-97 (Box 6, Folder 304)
    - Gore, John
      See: Series II, Writings, Harold Nicolson, research correspondence, Box 22, folder 923
    - Goudeket, Maurice, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 305)
      Copy of letter to John Phillips
      regarding Violiet Trefusis
    - Gould, Cecil, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 306)
    - Grafton, Hugh, Duke of, 1984-96 (Box 6, Folder 307)
    - Grant, Gerald, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 308)
    - Grant, Joy, 1986 Aug 28 (Box 6, Folder 309)
    - Grant, William A., 1987-97 (Box 6, Folder 310)
    - Gray, W. Forbes, 1948 Apr 21 (Box 6, Folder 311)
    - [Grenfell?], Violet, n.y. (Box 6, Folder 312)
    - Grigg, John, 1978-88 (Box 6, Folder 313)
    - Grimwade, Arthur, 1976 Jun 3 (Box 6, Folder 314)
    - Grylls, R. Glynn (Rosalie Mander), 1958-88 (Box 6, Folder 315)
    - Guinness, Alec, 1960-95 (Box 6, Folder 316)
    - Guinness, Bryan, 1984 Sep 2 (Box 6, Folder 317)
    - Guinness, Desmond, 1977, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 318)
    - Guinness, Jonathan, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 319)
    - "H" general, 1936-97 (Box 6, Folder 320)
    - Hall, David, 1986-95 (Box 6, Folder 321)
    - Hall, Jerry
      See: Mick Jagger, Box 8, folder 400
    - Hall, Julian, 1934-56 (Box 6, Folder 322)
    - Hall, Martin, 1985-86 (Box 6, Folder 323)
    - Hall, Roland, 1996 Apr 3 (Box 6, Folder 324)
    - Halle, Kay, 1939-86 (Box 6, Folder 325)
    - Hamilton, Ian, Sir; Hamilton, Jean, Lady, 1935-43 (Box 6, Folder 326)
      Christmas card for 1937
      includes photograph of the
      Hamiltons
    - Hamilton, Keith A., 1983, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 327)
    - Hamilton, Nigel, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 328)
    - Hamish Hamilton Ltd., 1967-87 (Box 6, Folder 329)
    - Hammersley, Violet, 1962 May 29 (Box 6, Folder 330)
    - Harris, John, 1955-88 (Box 6, Folder 331)
    - Harrison, Sunter, 1986-88 (Box 6, Folder 332)
    - Harrod, Wilhelmine Margaret Eve Cresswell, Lady ("Billa"), 1982-97, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 333)
    - Hart-Davis, Duff; Hart-Davis, Phyllida, 1991-96 (Box 6, Folder 334)
    - Hart-Davis, Rupert, 1926-95 (Box 7, Folder 335)
    - Harte, Glyn Boyd, 1976-94 (Box 7, Folder 336)
    - Hartley, L. P., 1969-70 (Box 7, Folder 337)
    - Haslam, Richard, 1987 Feb 28 (Box 7, Folder 338)
    - Hastings, Selina, 1982-97 (Box 7, Folder 339)
    - Hatchards Booksellers, 1995-96 (Box 7, Folder 340)
    - Hayter, Althea, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 341)
    - Healey, R. M., 1995 Mar 13 (Box 7, Folder 342)
    - Hazlehurst, Cameron, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 343)
    - Hayden, Ruth, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 344)
    - Henderson, Nicholas, Sir; Henderson, Mary, 1986-96 (Box 7, Folder 345)
    - Heslip, Joan, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 346)
    - Heuston, R. F. V., 1982 Mar 6 (Box 7, Folder 347)
    - Hicks, David, 1994-96, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 348)
    - Hickson, Alisdare, 1993 May 10 (Box 7, Folder 349)
    - Hildyard, Myles, 1950-97 (Box 7, Folder 350)
      Letter of 1991 Jul 3
      encloses a photo of a
      large house
    - Hill, Anne (Lady Anne Gathorne-Hardy), 1935-36 (Box 7, Folder 351-353)
      JL-M's outgoing letters
    - Hill, Anne (Lady Anne Gathorne-Hardy), 1941-97 (Box 7, Folder 354-355)
      Incoming letters to JL-M
    - Hill, Brian, 1975 Dec 10 (Box 7, Folder 356)
    - Hill, Derek, 1981-92, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 357)
    - Hill, Heywood
      See: G. Heywood Hill Ltd., Box 5, folder 275
    - Hill, Oliver, 1943 Feb 4 (Box 7, Folder 358)
    - Hill, Pamela, 1991-93 (Box 7, Folder 359)
    - Hilliard, Elizabeth, 1987-89 (Box 7, Folder 360)
      See also: Beckford Tower Trust, Box 1, folder 54
    - Hillier, Bevis, 1973-97 (Box 7, Folder 361)
    - Hitchen, Clive, 1994-96 (Box 8, Folder 362)
    - Hoare, Philip, 1988-95 (Box 8, Folder 363)
    - Hobhouse, Christopher, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 364)
    - Hobson, Anthony, 1988-97 (Box 8, Folder 365)
    - Hofstadter, Dan, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 366)
    - Holborne Museum and Craft Study Centre, 1989-90 (Box 8, Folder 367)
    - [Holland?], Guy; [Holland?], Joan, 1983-97 (Box 8, Folder 368)
    - Holroyd, Michael, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 369)
    - Honour, Hugh, 1961-86 (Box 8, Folder 370)
    - Hood, Peter, 1988-97 (Box 8, Folder 371)
    - Hornyold-Strickland, Henry, 1971 Aug 31 (Box 8, Folder 372)
    - Horseman, John; Horseman, Jill, 1992-94 (Box 8, Folder 373)
    - Houghton-Brown, Geoffrey, 1967-92 (Box 8, Folder 374)
    - Howard, Christopher H. D., 1988 Mar 23 (Box 8, Folder 375)
    - Howard, Jeremy, 1994-95 (Box 8, Folder 376)
    - Howard, Michael, 1982-86 (Box 8, Folder 377)
    - Howard, V. P. (Pam), 1990 (Box 8, Folder 378)
    - Houfe, Simon, 1981, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 379)
    - Hudson, Derek, 1988-96 (Box 8, Folder 380)
    - Humphries, Richard, 1989 Mar 29 (Box 8, Folder 381)
    - Hunter-Blair, David Oswald, Sir, Bart., 1935, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 382)
    - Hurley, Joan Mason (Joan Austen- Leigh), 1989-96 (Box 8, Folder 383)
    - Hussey, Betty; Hussey, Christopher, 1941-95 (Box 8, Folder 384)
      See also: Country Life, Box 3, folder 169
    - Hutchinson, Jeremy; Hutchinson, June, 1974-92 (Box 8, Folder 385)
    - Huxley, Elspeth, 1976-96 (Box 8, Folder 386)
    - Huxley, Gervas, 1970 Sep 2 (Box 8, Folder 387)
    - Hyde, H. Montgomery, 1983, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 388)
    - Hyslop, Paul, 1980-88 (Box 8, Folder 389)
    - "I" general, 1942-93, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 390)
    - Imperial War Museum, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 391)
    - The Independent
      See: Jamie Fergusson, Box 5, folder 250
    - Ingram, Richard, 1997 Jul 9 (Box 8, Folder 392)
      See also: The Oldie, Box 12, folder 580
    - Innes-Smith, Robert, 1991-97 (Box 8, Folder 393)
    - Insall, Donald W., 1957 Dec 2 (Box 8, Folder 394)
    - Irish Guards, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 395)
    - Isham, Gyles, Sir, Bart., 1953-54 (Box 8, Folder 396)
    - Ison, Walter William, 1978 Apr 17 (Box 8, Folder 397)
    - "J" general, 1957-97 (Box 8, Folder 398)
    - Jackson-Stops, Gervase, 1983-95 (Box 8, Folder 399)
    - Jagger, Mick; Jagger, Jerry (Jerry Hall), [1994], n.d. (Box 8, Folder 400)
    - James, Robert Rhodes
      See: Series II, Writings, The Enigmatic Edwardian, Box 21, folder 910
    - Jebb, Miles, 1990-91 (Box 8, Folder 401)
    - Jellico, George, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 402)
    - Jenkins, Jennifer, Dame, 1993-97 (Box 8, Folder 403)
    - Jennings, Derek, 1989-92 (Box 8, Folder 404)
    - Jenyns, Soame, 1975 Oct 29 (Box 8, Folder 405)
    - Jersey, George Francis Child-Villiers, Earl of ("Grandy"), 1950-95 (Box 8, Folder 406)
    - Jervis, Simon, 1988 Mar 3 (Box 8, Folder 407)
    - John, Augustus, 1940 Mar 10 (Box 8, Folder 408)
    - John Murray Ltd., 1971-97 (Box 8, Folder 409)
    - Johnson, Babs
      See: Georgina Masson, Box 11, folder 518
    - Johnson, Joan M., 1995-96 (Box 8, Folder 410)
    - Johnson, Susannah, 1990-96, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 411)
    - Johnston, Nicholas; Johnston, Rosie, 1990, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 412)
    - Joliffe, John, 1983-94 (Box 8, Folder 413)
      See also: National Art-Collections Fund, Box 12, folder 563
    - Jones, Roderick, Sir
      See: Reuters Ltd., Box 13, folder 635
    - Jones, Stephen, 1990-92 (Box 8, Folder 414)
    - Jourdain, Margaret, 1945-48, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 415)
    - "K" general, 1944-97 (Box 8, Folder 416)
    - Keen, Mary, 1988-97 (Box 8, Folder 417)
    - Kellaway, Deborah, 1995 Feb 9 (Box 8, Folder 417a)
    - Kelly, Felix, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 418)
    - Kennedy, General Sir John, 1970 May 9 (Box 8, Folder 419)
    - Kennet, Edward Hilton Young, Baron, 1937-47 (Box 8, Folder 420)
    - Kennet, Kathleen Young, Lady (Kathleen Scott), 1935-45, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 421)
    - Kennet, Wayland Hilton Young, Baron, 1947, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 422)
    - Kent, Prince Michael of; Kent, Princess Michael of, 1987-96 (Box 8, Folder 423)
      Christmas cards include photographs
      of the couple with their children,
      Lord Frederick and Lady Gabriella
      Windsor
    - Kenworthy-Browne, John, 1959-97 (Box 9, Folder 424-426)
    - Keppel, Aluska, 1990-93 (Box 9, Folder 427)
    - Keppel, Sonia, 1984 Aug 8 (Box 9, Folder 428)
    - Ketton-Cremer, Robert Wyndham, 1948 May 17 (Box 9, Folder 429)
    - Kirsting, A. F., 1988 Aug 8 (Box 9, Folder 430)
    - King, Francis, 1981 Feb 4 (Box 9, Folder 431)
    - Kingsley, Nicholas, 1989 Jun 19, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 432)
    - Kinross, Patrick Balfour, Baron, 1933-76 (Box 9, Folder 433)
    - Kitz, Norman, 1986 Jan 19 (Box 9, Folder 434)
    - Knollys, Eardley, 1958-91, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 435-437)
    - Knox, George, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 438)
    - Knox, James, 1990-97 (Box 9, Folder 439)
    - Kolb, Philip, 1977 Nov 17 (Box 9, Folder 440)
    - Kornbluth, Jesse, 1986 Jul 2 (Box 9, Folder 441)
    - Kuhn, William M., 1986 Feb 14 (Box 9, Folder 442)
    - "L" general, 1941-97 (Box 9, Folder 443)
    - Laing, Alastair, 1991 Nov 13 (Box 9, Folder 444)
    - Lambert, Angela, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 445)
    - Lambton, Tim, 1990-97 (Box 9, Folder 446)
    - Lamont-Brown, Raymond, 1993 Nov 26 (Box 9, Folder 447)
    - Lancaster, Nancy, 1977-92 (Box 9, Folder 448)
    - Lancaster, Osbert, Sir; Lancaster, Anne, 1981-96, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 449)
    - Lancelot, Alain, 1991 Aug 2 (Box 9, Folder 450)
    - Langberg, Harald, 1952 May 20 (Box 9, Folder 451)
    - Lascelles, Alan, Sir, 1957 Aug 16 (Box 9, Folder 452)
    - Lawrence, A. W., 1962 Sep 9 (Box 9, Folder 453)
    - Leeper, Janet, 1941 Sep 1, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 454)
    - Lehmann, John, 1959 Mar 18 (Box 9, Folder 455)
    - Lehmann, Rosamond, 1953-88 (Box 9, Folder 456)
    - Lehmann, Rosamond, 1953-88 (Box 10, Folder 457-458)
    - LeJeune, Anthony, 1991 Oct 20 (Box 10, Folder 459)
    - Lennox-Boyd, Alan Tindal, 1941, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 460)
    - Leslie, Anita Shane, 1936 Feb 2 (Box 10, Folder 461)
      See also: Series II, Writings, The Enigmatic Edwardian, Box 21, folder 910
    - Leslie, Shane, 1932 Dec (Box 10, Folder 462)
    - L'Etang, Hugh, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 463)
    - Levi, Peter; Levi, Dierdre, 1990-97, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 464)
    - Lewis, Jeremy, 1992 Jul 8, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 465)
      See also: Chatto and Windus, Box 3, folder 129
    - Licht, Meg, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 466)
    - Lieberman, Sally, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 467)
    - Lindsay, Loelia, Duchess of Westminster (Box 10, Folder 468)
    - Lister, Ted, 1939-42 (Box 10, Folder 469)
    - Little, Brown and Company, 1966-68 (Box 10, Folder 470)
    - Littlejohn, David, 1994 Apr 25 (Box 10, Folder 471)
    - Llewellyn, Hoël, 1927-34, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 472)
    - Lloyd of Dolobran, George Ambrose Lloyd, Baron (Lord Lloyd), 1932-1940, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 473)
    - Lloyd, Blanche, Lady, 1936-66 (Box 10, Folder 474)
    - Lloyd, David, 1964-83 (Box 10, Folder 475)
    - Lloyd, Jean, 1986-94, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 476)
    - Lloyd George, Owen, 1994-96 (Box 10, Folder 477)
    - Lockhart, Robert Bruce Hamilton, Sir
      See: Series II, Writings, Correspondence of Harold Nicolson, Box 23, folder 945